planetgr.com 2006-10-21

# planetGR! Privacy Policy

**planetGR!** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this   
Web site: [planetGR!](http://www.planetgr.com/)

**Advertisers**   
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

* Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies. 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. **planetGR!** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  **Special Relationships**  
This site also may use "co-branding" with outside advertisers, so that the connection between our site and that of the advertiser is "seamless." These "co-branded" pages may be used by an outside ad company to display ads on our site. While we do not use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. **Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  **E-mail**  
Click on the below links for our E-mail Privacy Policy and Terms Of Use.   
[Privacy Policy ](http://mail.bigmailbox.com/users/planetgrcom/signup.cgi?sw=1&tt=full) \- [Terms of Service ](http://mail.bigmailbox.com/users/planetgrcom/terms.cgi) **Forms**   
Our site uses forms for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information. Contact information from the forms is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary and is not shared with other companies.  **Data Quality/Access**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can send email to [admin@planetgr.com](mailto:admin@planetgr.com)

**Contacting planetGR!**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
